// Francisco Javier Fuentes Diaz, Master in Telecommunications, UAB 2021, Spain.

The RV32I has full support on the base instruction set I.
The RV32IM has full support on the expansion set M, the 
following estimations are using the dDIVrest32u and MULDIV2 
options at the config_core.vh file. Different combinations 
will have different frequency and resource performances.
The RV32IMF has full support on the expansion set M and only 
supports S format of the expansion set F on a limited number 
of instructions, including FLW, FSW, FADD and FSUB (FPU and 
ADDSUB_FPs modules) instructions.

The following estimations are in MHz and Logic Elements on 
the target FPGA platform of the project, check MULDIV 
performances.txt for many explainations that can be used 
also here.

________________|_RV32InoPipe*_|_RV32I_|_RV32IM_|_RV32IMF_|
Max. Freq. 85ºC |          3.0 |  57.7 |   41.6 |    18.5 |
Max. Freq. 0ºC  |          3.3 |  63.1 |   46.0 |    20.6 |
Resource alloc. |        2,465 | 3,520 |  5,125 |   8,566 |

*: The RV32I no pipeline core version is just a registerless 
version of the RV32I pipeline at the stages. I'm not sure if 
works correctly, as many combinational loops were found at the 
synthesis, but that's normal because I'm leaveing many 
functionalities to get around between register's stages that 
aren't around anymore in that version (like the forwarding)... 
so it may not work, but I think is useful to make performance 
estimation of a single-cycle RV32I core.
I didn't use Pau's core because it did implement many latches 
that I was unable to get out, so the estimations I was getting 
with that core were wrong.