Check MULDIV performance.txt for more explainations that can be used 
also at this module.

________________|_ADDSUB_FPs_|_FPU_(contains ADDSUB_FPs)_|
Max. Freq. 85ºC |   22.0 MHz |                  22.6 MHz |
Max. Freq. 0ºC  |   24.3 MHz |                  24.9 MHz |
Resource alloc. |  938   LE  |               1,002   LE  |

Why the FPU that contains the module ADDSUB_FPs has higher frequency 
than the ADDSUB_FPs module alone? That's a great question... no idea. 
I suppose that with the added logic, the synthesis tool manages to 
route the logic better by the default option of optimization routing.

With how low is the frequency, my sugestion is to make it take two 
or even three clock cycles, so you can duplicate or triplicate this 
maximum frequency. Man, how many hours gone with this and is pretty 
crap... I hope all the test I've gone through makes it work properly.


// Francisco Javier Fuentes Diaz 5-Jan-2021 UAB Telecommunication Master